ac-pocketcamp.com 2019-12-31

# Nintendo Privacy Policy - Official Site

At Nintendo, we know your privacy is very important to you, so please take the time to carefully read our privacy policy. Our policy is designed to help you understand the types of information that we collect, how we use and share the information and how the information is protected. This privacy policy applies to all Nintendo services that directly reference or link to this policy, but does not apply to Nintendo services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this policy.

* ## Categories of information we collect

  * **Information that you give to us**

When you register for and use our services we collect the information that you give to us. This may include information like your name, email address, phone number, date of birth, country of residence, language, gender, and time zone.

  * **Information about your device**

When you use our services we may collect specific information about your device, and across your devices, such as the product model, serial number, operating system, device settings, device performance, device and advertising identifiers, Internet service provider, IP address and other unique personal or online identifiers. If you or your device experiences an error, we collect information about the error, the time the error occurred, the application or features being used, the state of the application when the error occurred, and any communications or content provided at the time the error occurred.

  * **Information about your use of our services**

We collect information about your use of and interaction with our services. This could include information about your gameplay, your online status, your service use history, your connections and interactions with other users, the content you share, the date and time of your visit, information about the links you click, pages you view, and advertising you interact with within our services, inferences used to create a profile about preferences and characteristics, standard server log information, and other information about how you use our services.

  * **Your content**

With your consent, we may collect and process information about your precise location. When we have your location information, we use it to tailor our services for you and others, like helping you establish friend relationships with other Nintendo users or telling your existing friends that you are nearby.

  * **Your purchases**

Some of our services allow you to make purchases. If you use any of our services to make a purchase, we may collect information about the purchase. This could include payment information, such as your credit card number, account authentication information, and contact information like your billing and shipping address.

  * **Location information**

With your consent, we may collect and process information about your precise location. When we have your location information, we use it to tailor our services for you and others, like helping you establish friend relationships with other Nintendo users.

  * **Information from other sources**

We may also receive information about you from other sources, including from users of our services, entities that sell information, and third-party services and organizations. For example, if you access any social media or similar services through our services to login or to share information about your experience on our services with others, we may collect information from these third-party services.

  * **Aggregated and deidentified information**

We may aggregate or de-identify the information described above. Aggregated or de-identified information is not subject to this policy.

* ## How we use your information

We use the information that you give us and the information we collect to deliver, maintain and improve our services, including troubleshooting, data analytics, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes. We also use this information to provide you with services that you request, develop new services, suggest personally relevant features, offer you customized content, allow you to participate in interactive features of our services, manage accounts, provide you with tailored advertising, send you promotional materials from us or our affiliates and trusted business partners, keep our services, business and users safe and secure, comply with applicable laws and regulations, and to protect or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

Whenever you contact us, we use the information that you provide to us to help resolve issues you might be having when you use our services. We also use information, such as your email address or phone number, to respond to you when you contact us, to let you know about changes to our policies and terms, to let you know about changes or improvements to our services and to inform you about other services that we offer.

We may use cookies, or other similar technologies, on some of the features of our services. Cookies are small files that are typically downloaded to the browser application on your device. Cookies help us to ensure the safety and smooth functioning of certain features of our services and they also help us to collect information about your user preferences. We sometimes use information collected from cookies to improve your user experience and the quality of our services. For example, by saving your user preferences, we may be able to customize our services in ways that you prefer. You may be able to disable cookies in your browser settings or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being used. If you disable cookies, you may not be able to use all of the features of our services. Some web browsers may transmit "do not track" signals. We currently do not take action in response to these signals.

We use certain third-party partners that collect information when you use some of our services. These third-parties use cookies, web beacons, software development kits (SDKs), and similar technologies to collect and analyze crash reports, keep track of what content or ads you view, how long you spend on different pages, how you arrived on a particular page and how you respond to the ads we show you. These third parties may combine the information they collect from our services with other information they collect from other sites and services.  The practices of our third-party partners are governed by their own privacy policies. The third-parties with whom we work include, but are not limited to, those partners listed on the page linked below. Some of these third-parties, including those listed on the page linked below, may give users choices about how they collect and use your information.

We also may permit our third-party partners to set cookies and use web beacons, SDKs, and similar technologies within our services to help us perform various internal functions necessary to operate our business and to collect information about your use of our and others’ services across your devices. These third-parties may use that information to provide you advertisements, across different sites, services and devices, about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Some of these third-parties may offer you a way to opt-out of this type of targeted advertising through industry choice mechanisms. To learn more about third-parties that participate in these choice offerings and to exercise choices that may be available to you, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/) and [www.aboutads.info](https://www.aboutads.info/). You may also be able to opt out from targeted advertising through the advertising settings for your mobile device.

We do not, and will not sell your personal information to third parties. However, we do permit third-parties to collect certain personal information, as described above, through some of our services and share personal information with third parties for business purposes as described in this policy, including but not limited to providing advertising on our services and elsewhere based on users’ online activities over time and across different sites, services, and devices. The information practices of these third parties are not covered by this privacy policy.

* ## How your information is shared

We sometimes share your information within our family of Nintendo companies and with trusted third-party partners outside of Nintendo for processing. We may also share your information for other legal and business purposes, such as complying with legal process, responding to claims or inquiries, enforcing our terms, or protecting the rights, property or personal safety of our operations, our users, or the public. Your information may also be shared as part of any sale or transfer of company assets, if legally permitted.

If you choose to connect with a third-party service through our services, we may share your information with that service and that service may share your information with us. The use of your information, and the use of cookies, web beacons, or other technologies, by these third-party providers is subject to their own privacy policies.

Some of our services allow you to share information and content with others. When you decide to use these services, the information or content that you share, your online status, and your gameplay information may be visible to Nintendo and its trusted business partners, other Nintendo users, and in some cases the public. Please keep in mind, when you use these services, that the information and content that you choose to share can be read, collected, or used by others. You are fully responsible for the information and content that you choose to share in these instances.

  * **Authorized third-party service providers**

We share your information with third-party service providers that provide services to us for a variety of business purposes, such as payment processing, customer service, email deployment, advertising and marketing (including counting ad impressions, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, ensuring compliance with industry standards and specifications, ad delivery, reporting, personalization, audience segmentation, and analytics), security and performance monitoring, maintaining or servicing accounts, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, information hosting, auditing, and information processing.

  * **Corporate affiliates**

We sometimes share your information within our family of Nintendo companies.

  * **Legal purposes**

We may share your information to comply with legal process, respond to claims or inquiries, enforce our terms, or protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of our operations, our users, or the public.

  * **Business transfers**

We may share your information as part of a substantial corporate transaction, such as a sale or transfer of company assets, a merger, consolidation, or as otherwise legally permitted.

  * **Other users and the public**

Some of our services allow you to share information and content with others or engage in public activities. When you decide to use these services, the information or content that you share, your nickname, your user icon, your online status, and your gameplay information may be visible to Nintendo and its trusted business partners, other Nintendo users, and in some cases the public. Please keep in mind, when you use these service, that the information and content that you choose to share can be read, collected, or used by others. You are fully responsible for the information and content that you choose to share in these instances.

  * **When you access third-party services**

If you access third-party services -- such as third-party online gaming services and social media services -- through our services, these third-party services may be able to collect information about you, including information about your activity on our services, and they may notify your connections on the third-party services about your use of our services, in accordance with their own privacy policies.

  * **With your consent**

We may share information for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect the information or pursuant to your consent.

* ## Your controls, choices and rights

We may offer you certain controls and choices regarding the information we collect, how the information is used, and how it is shared. These controls and choices may include the ability to update, correct or delete information that you have provided to us or information that we have collected through your use of our services. They may also include the ability to opt-out of receiving notifications, promotions, offers or other advertising from us.

Depending on your jurisdiction, you may have the right, in accordance with applicable law, to request access to, deletion, and portability of your information. For information on how to submit such a request go [here](https://www.nintendo.com/privacy-request/).

We will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights and choices, although some of the functionality and features available on our services may change or no longer be available to you.

* ## Information retention and information security

Personal information will be retained only for so long as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy, in accordance with applicable laws. We have implemented administrative, physical and technical security measures that are designed to protect your information from loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. You should understand though that, despite our efforts, no security can be guaranteed as impenetrable. Please note that information collected by third parties may not have the same security protections as information you submit to us, and we are not responsible for protecting the security of such information.

* ## Information about children

We do not knowingly collect, use or share personal information from children under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent or as permitted by law. Where a parent or legal guardian has provided consent, the child may be able to use his or her Nintendo Account to play certain third-party games and applications that are not published by Nintendo. Parents or guardians may review, modify, or delete the child’s personal information, or withdraw consent, by contacting us using the contact information provided at the end of this privacy policy, and may manage which third-party games and applications can access and use the child’s Nintendo Account information through your Nintendo Account profile settings.

* ## Changes

Nintendo may update this privacy policy from time to time. When we update it, we will revise the "Last Updated" date above. If we make material changes in the way we collect, use, retain or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending you an email at the last email address that you provided us, or by posting notice of the changes on the services covered by this privacy policy.

* ## ESRB Certification

This privacy policy and the certification seal located on our websites that link to this policy confirms that we are a valid licensee, and participating member, of the Entertainment Software Rating Board's Privacy Certified Program. To help protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative. As a licensee in this privacy certification program, we are subject to frequent audits of our websites and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by the ESRB. All of our sites containing the ESRB certification seal have been reviewed, and certified, by ESRB to meet established online information collection and use practices.

* ## Contact information

If you have any questions, concerns or comments regarding this privacy policy, or any of our privacy practices, please contact us via email at privacypolicy@noa.nintendo.com, via phone at 1-888-977-7627, or via regular mail at Nintendo of America Inc., Attn: Privacy Administrator, 4600 150th Avenue NE, Redmond, WA 98052, U.S.A.

You may also contact ESRB Privacy Certified via email at privacy@esrb.org, or via regular mail at ESRB Privacy Certified, Attn: Privacy Certified Program, 420 Lexington Avenue, Suite 2024, New York, NY 10170.

END
